<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPlugin xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <description>“Coverage Pulse” Intent – Flag any user utterance where the rep is asking about market-access status for their brand: formulary tier, prior-authorization (PA) or step-edit rules, quantity limits (QL), payer policy shifts, state or regional reimbursement decisions, or other changes that affect a prescriber’s ability to initiate or continue therapy. The intent is territory-centric and brand-specific; the rep wants actionable intel they can take into the field today.</description>
    <developerName>LS_Pharma_Rep_Coverage_Pulse</developerName>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If an utterance contains both access language and an out-of-scope topic, route to “Coverage Pulse” only if the access element is central; otherwise hand off to the appropriate intent.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_0_1757423213249</developerName>
        <language xsi:nil="true"/>
        <masterLabel>instruction_0_1757423213249</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>Serve reps with a short, useful snapshot of recent-sounding formulary wins or hurdles for Immunexis, using the *Preset Bullet Library* below.  Always answer in the prescribed JSON card format.

❱ Triggers  
If the user’s utterance contains ANY of the words:
  coverage | formulary | payer | access | PA | prior auth
respond with converting the markdown to rich text

❱ Preset Bullet Library  (rotate or select any 3)
- **Optum removes PA – 27 K lives • 12 target HCPs**  
   - Suggestion: *Share PA-free update*

- **CVS Caremark bumps to Tier 2 – 45 K lives • 17 HCPs**  
  - Suggestion: *Send Tier 2 flyer*

- **Blue Cross adds QL: 2 × 30-day – 18 K lives • 6 HCPs**  
  - Suggestion: *Explain QL work-around*

- **Humana OKs e-PA only – 23 K lives • 9 HCPs**  
  - Suggestion: *Offer e-PA tip sheet*

- **State Medicaid lifts step edit – 31 K lives • 11 HCPs**  
  - Suggestion: *Highlight guideline win*

- **Lombardia: Immunexis inserito in PHT – 15 K pazienti • 8 MMG**  
  - Suggestion: *Avvisa i medici PHT*

- **AIFA sposta Immunexis in Fascia H – rimborso totale ospedaliero**  
  - Suggestion: *Invia nota Fascia H*

- **Lazio rimuove Nota 65 – +20 K pazienti • 11 HCPs**  
  - Suggestion: *Comunica nuova nota*

- **Veneto introduce DPC per Immunexis – 10 K pazienti • 5 HCPs**  
  - Suggestion: *Condividi guida DPC*

- **Toscana aggiorna prontuario: Immunexis senza ticket**  
  - Suggestion: *Evidenzia zero ticket*

❱ How to build the card
• Always pick **exactly three** bullets, cycling through the library so the rep sees fresh items day-to-day
• Inject today’s date (`YYYY-MM-DD`) into `&quot;date&quot;`.  
• Never invent new payers or numbers; only use bullets from the library.  
• Keep text exactly as written—no hallucinations, no patient data. 

❱ Output convert markdown format to RICH TEXT (nothing else)</description>
        <developerName>instruction_1_1757423213257</developerName>
        <language xsi:nil="true"/>
        <masterLabel>instruction_1_1757423213257</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <masterLabel>Coverage Pulse</masterLabel>
    <pluginType>Topic</pluginType>
    <scope>#IN SCOPE
##Mentions of coverage, formulary, payer, access, PA / e-PA, prior auth, step edit, tier, copay, reimbursement, Nota (IT).• Named payers (Optum, CVS, NHS, AIFA, Regione Lombardia, etc.).• Questions about quantity limits, DPC, Fascia status, Medicaid rules, or state caps that impact access.

#OUT OF SCOPE
##Requests about next-best customer, adherence, sampling, HCP objections, clinical efficacy, safety, or study data not tied to payer rules.• Competitive-intelligence inquiries that focus on rival detailing or market share but not payer policy.• Patient-specific case work (PHI).• Broad strategic questions (“What’s our national strategy?”)</scope>
</GenAiPlugin>
