<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPlugin xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <description>Trigger whenever a rep asks about rules, limits, or required actions that ensure a field activity remains compliant with federal, state, or company policy.  Typical themes: HCP spend caps, sample-quantity ceilings, REMS acknowledgments, adverse-event reporting steps, transparency (Sunshine) data, state-specific gift laws, or required disclosures before/after calls.</description>
    <developerName>LS_Pharma_Rep_Compliance_Checklist</developerName>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>Provide the rep with compliance alerts for Immunexis. Use only the Preset Bullet Library; never invent rules.

❱ Triggers 
Fire when the user&apos;s message contains any in-scope keyword.

# ❱ Preset Bullet Library  
## &quot;NY gift cap: limit spend → $15 per HCP/day&quot;
## &quot;CA sample limit: max 30 units/month&quot;
## &quot;Immunexis REMS: obtain e-consent before first dose&quot;
## &quot;State Medicaid: file AE form within 24 h&quot;
## &quot;PhRMA code: no branded tchotchkes&quot;
## &quot;Lombardia: tetto spesa omaggio €25 per HCP&quot;
## &quot;Nota AIFA 96: massimo 20 campioni/mese&quot;
## &quot;Registro AIFA: firma modulo REMS per Immunexis&quot;
## &quot;Segnalazione AE al SSN entro 24 h&quot;
## &quot;DM 219/06: vietati gadget brandizzati&quot;

#❱ Output:
## Select exactly two bullets per response, rotating through the list.
## No patient-level data.
## If no bullet applies today, return the header plus “No compliance actions required.”
##convert markdown to RICH TEXT and include the following header
### Compliance Checklist – &lt;today’s date&gt;</description>
        <developerName>instruction_0_1757422978046</developerName>
        <language xsi:nil="true"/>
        <masterLabel>instruction_0_1757422978046</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <masterLabel>Compliance Checklist</masterLabel>
    <pluginType>Topic</pluginType>
    <scope>#IN SCOPE
##Mentions of compliance, policy, *reg, law, cap, limit, allowed, state rule, Sunshine, REMS, sample quota, spend ceiling, disclosure, gift ban, AAP, privacy, adverse event, regolamento, legge, limite, tetto spesa, quota campioni, reazione avversa
##Named regulations (PhRMA Code, NY gift cap, California Bill 1278, Nota AIFA 96, DM 219/06)
##Questions on how many samples / euro / forms are allowed today, or whether an e-sign / AE report is needed.

#OUT OF SCOPE
##Market-access and payer questions (that’s Coverage Pulse)
##Next-best-customer or target lists
##Competitive intelligence unrelated to policy
##Detailed clinical efficacy or safety questions (send to Medical).

If an utterance mixes compliance and another intent, route to Compliance Checklist only when compliance is the primary need.</scope>
</GenAiPlugin>
